CHAITRA DESHPANDE

ENGINEER (INFORMATION SCIENCE)

CONTACT

Permenant Address- Flt No 203 Green Horizon Apt. 10th Cross Bhagyanagar, Tilakwadi Belagavi. 590006

Current Address- Flt No 19, Madhav Residency, Upper Khopoli, Balwadi Khopoli Raigad, 410203

Contact +91 7349755769

Mailchaitradeshpandebgm@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering Information Science VTU 2016–2019 7.85CGPA

Diploma
Computer Science
Board Of Technical Education,
Banglore
2013-2016
73.23%

SSLC Karnataka Secondary Education Board 2012-2013 79.84%

SKILLS

- JAVA
- SOL
- Html
- Css
- Bootstrap
- Framework Code Integrator

PROFILE

To seek an entry level position to begin my career, that can provide steady growth and learning opportunity and practical experience extensively, where I can apply my technical knowledge, acquire new skills and work closely with highly experienced professionals.

TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

JAVA

- Good knowledge in Classes and Objects
- Proficient in Constructors
- Well known to OOPS concepts
- Familiar with Method Overloading and Method Overriding
- Threads(basics)
- Good Knowledge about Object class, String class ,stringBuffer class
- Good knowledge on Data Structures concepts like Stack, Queue.
- Good at Interface.

SQL

- Good Knowledge in using RDBMS Application
- Well known to Clauses
- Proficient in Functions and Types of Functions
- Good knowledge in joins and Types of Joins
- Familiar with SubQuery

WEB DEVELOPMENT

- Html
- Css
- Bootstrap
- javascript

CERTIFICATIONS

- 1. Cambridge Business English Certification(B1 level).
- 2. Internshala Online "Web Development" Certification.

PERSONAL SNIPETS

Name – Chaitra Deshpande

Father's Name – Venkatesh Deshpande

Place – Belagavi, Karnataka

DOB: 01-May-1997

Marital Status: Married

Languages Known: Kannada, English, Hindi, Marathi

Hobbies & Interest: Dancing, Travelling, Anchoring Etc.

SOFT SKILLS

Hard Working

Loyal

Consistent

Eye on Detailing

Goal Oriented

WORK EXPERIENCE

1) <u>Company - Fedilis Corporate Services Pvt. Ltd.</u> (Providing services to HP Clients as Contract Worker)

- Designation- Technical Support Engineer
- Duration- Feb 2022 to Aug 2022
- Location- Bangalore (WFH during Covid-19)
- Roles & Responsibilities-
 - 1) Getting issues raised by clients and analyzing solutions and giving appropriate support via chat.
 - 2) Creating cases based on necessary situations.

2) <u>Company – Vritika Technologies</u>

- Designation- Web Designer at Vritika Technologies
- Duration- 3 Months (July 2020 to October2020)
- Location- Belagavi
- Roles & Responsibilities-
 - 1) Modifying the existing websites according to Client's requirement.
 - 2) Creating Website from Scratch as per the requirement.

ACADEMIC PROJECT

1. **Project Title**: "CHILD SECURITY ALERTSYSTEM".

Description: RFID based child security system for a school bus which will help the parents and the school to keep track of the child's location. Every student's entry and exit activities will be informed to the parents by generating SMS.

2. Project Title: "BUSTRACKING".

Description: This project aims to build an Android application that automates all the aspects related to the college bus arrival. At specific pickup point the application sends SMS to students who are supposed to board the bus at the next pickup point. The message is received within the restricted range.

INTERNSHIP

Organization: Scalebytes, Belagavi

Duration: 20/06/2018 to 20/08/2018

Key learnings: I have learnt the concepts of Big Data Technology and hence applied the concepts on few data sets

like student details and executed the queries.

Place – Belagavi

SIGNATURE

DATE -

Chaitra Deshpande